

DANIEL FAIGENBOIM

Developer

- Castelar, Bs As, Argentina
- daniel.fai89@gmail.com
- +541158056091
- https://github.com/danifai

TECHNOLOGIES

- Python
- Autocad
- Javascript
 Maya
- NodeJs
- Blender
- ReactJs
- Shotgun
- HTML
- Office
- CSS
- MvSOL
- Github

ABOUT ME

"I am motivated to work with technologies and learn something new every day. I have extensive experience working in multidisciplinary teams and a broad background in logic.

My goal is to develop myself by applying the knowledge I have acquired through my studies, striving to ensure that my contribution is noticeable and with opportunities for growth based on my performance."

WORK HISTORY

11/2022-Present Python Developer Many-Worlds Studios - Programming

- Pipeline Integration and Development: Specialized in utilizing Python API for the creation and maintenance of efficient, automated pipelines in VFX projects.
- Development, debugging and updating code for custom tools and plugins for Autodesk Maya and Blender, Python.
- Integration of design software with generative AI of texts and images.

03/2022-09/2022

Fullstack Web Developer Tecnofan.com - Programming

- Integrative project for the educational environment of Digital House.
- Development of ecommerce using agile methodologies and Git for version control.
- Backend: database interaction, MVC, CRUD, validations.
- Frontend: responsive views, styling, client-side interaction and validations.
- Technologies: JavaScript, Node.js, React.js, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Git, Trello.

04/2021-10/2022

Technical Designer Aluminum and PVC Openings

Veka Argentina (04/2022-10/2022) Aberturas Rosch (04/2021 - 04/2022)

- Technical assistance and training to manufacturers.
- Review and generation of technical documentation in Autocad and Winmaker.
- Calculation and quotation of materials.
- Layout and monitoring of construction projects.
- Customer service during construction process and after-sales.

05/2010-03/2021

Civil Drafter - Civil Engineering

Geodata S.p.A. (09/2020-03/2021)

Ministry of Transportation of the Nation (02/2019 - 01/2020)

Geoconsult S.A. (08/2013 - 12/2018) CH2M HILL S.A. (05/2011 - 07/2013)

Labor Corporativa S.A. (05/2010 - 05/2011)

• Documentation in Autocad and Civil 3D for metal structures and reinforced concrete, topographic and road plans.

04/2008-04/2010

CAD Drafter Mobiliarios Fontenla S.A. - Design

• Drawing of technical plans in Autocad. Customer and technical support.

EDUCATION

2022-Present University Technician in Artificial Intelligence

Universidad Nacional de Hurlingham - Argentina

2022-Present University Technician in Programming

Universidad Nacional de Hurlingham - Argentina

2022 Python Developer

Universidad Nacional de San Luis - Argentina Programa 4.0

2022 Fullstack Web Developer

Digital House

2007-2018

Civil Engineering - Coursed up to 4th level.

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional (UTN)

LANGUAGES

ADITIONAL

Spanish: Native

English: Intermediate

Driver's license B1 Own vehicle